Hello and welcome to another walkthrough for computer architecture for everybody. In this
I want to do an assignment and so sometimes when you launch this you will have an assignment and
that assignment will be autograded. So we're going to build a simple AND gate circuit with
two inputs and one output. So let's go ahead and do that. Let's place an AND gate. Now
let's let's turn on the command and let's use let's say place and and then say place input.
Place input. So, we got some inputs. I don't remember the syntax to connect them. So,
we got I'm going to move them around and make them line up a little bit. I'm going to
connect the inputs to the the two inputs to the ANDgate. And then I'm going to place an output.
put the output here. And then we'll test to see.
Oh, come on. Connect.
There we go. Now it's connected. Okay. So, we've got our ANDgate working. 01 1 011. And it's a one.
Okay. So, let's go ahead and do the autograder. So, we haven't done everything yet. It gives you a
truth table. So we can say start grading and it's going to say ooh it's looking for input labeled A.
I found inputs one and input two. Please use the tag tool to label your inputs. Okay. And so we are
going to do that. We're going to use the tag tool to call this one input A. Okay. And we're going to
use tag tool to mention this one as B. This is a pretty simple assignment. Uh and let's still make
a mistake. We got to connect the output to Q. But let's just let's start the grading. Missing
output label Q. Fix it. Fix it with the tag tool. So we'll go ahead and call this Q. And then you
can see it's going to autograde. And this time it's going to hopefully work. So it says, okay,
we found all the required components. All the required components are properly labeled A, B,
and Q. Then it says it's got it. We got an ANDgate. That's cool.
So let's just see if zero a of 0 b of zero results in an output of zero. And it does.
Let's try an a of zero and b of one. Does it and output does it produce an output of zero? Yes,
it does. And does it an a of one and b of zero produce a zero? Yes,
it does. And the last test is the one and the one and it gives us an and and sends
great back to the learning management system. So I hope you found this useful. Uh, cheers.